Silver Judgment!
Every wave of monsters I defeat
is followed by yet another.
Aunt Hilde is running around the
kingdom putting up barriers,
but at this rate,
pillars of light won't be enough.
Prince Julius refuses to acknowledge
the danger, no matter how I push.
He even refused the aid
of the Parnacortan knights
that my sister tried to send.
I can feel its presence viscerally.
The Demon Realm is close
enough for that, and yet...
We've no time left to lose.
Unless I depose Prince Julius,
this kingdom has no future.
I will protect it.
I am the saint of this kingdom!
I will... won't I?
Big Sister Philia?
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 9
"Crossroads of Fate"
That's a pretty crazy
idea you came up with...
Using a magic-convergence spell
to expand the Great Purification Circle
to encompass the surrounding kingdoms.
A brilliant plan, Miss Greatest.
Or so I'd like to say, but...
Will it be in time?
I believe so, yes.
Well, it will certainty
turn things around if it is.
But what if you fail?
Big Sis, don't be so pessimi—
You stay out of this.
In all honesty, how many days
do you think Girtonia has left?
Around four, I believe.
Is that true?
Prince Reichardt...
Please, allow me to make introductions.
These are—
Erza Notice, exorcist.
And this is my familiar, Mammon.
Heyo.
I believe the church should have
informed you of our arrival.
Indeed, they did.
Philia, we received word
from the knights we deployed.
I'm afraid they were turned
away at the border.
They were even falsely accused
of exploiting the situation to invade.
Our knights are a cornerstone
of our defense, on par with a saint.
If Girtonia really only has four days...
I may have to order them to return.
Yeah, that would be good.
Big Sis!
If a path to the Demon Realm
forms in Girtonia,
the awakening of Archdemon Asmodeus
will soon follow.
Even with the circle protecting you,
not even Parnacorta may remain unscathed.
After all...
You, Saint Philia, are the one he's after.
So, Miss Greatest, are you
aware of the cycle of rebirth?
Of course I am.
The Church of Cremoux teaches that
even when we die and our bodies decay,
our souls remain, reborn anew
on and on for eternity.
And where do you think the soul of Fiana,
the saint who sealed Asmodeus away, ended up?
Fiana's soul...?
I'll tell you.
It's right there.
The soul of Archsaint Fiana resides in you.
Which is why we're seeing presages of his
return as the Demon Realm grows closer.
Oh, sweet love!
Love?
Don't ask me how, but he fell for the
archsaint over the course of their battle.
Getting a beating from a gorgeous babe...
Must've awakened something in old
Asmodeus, if you catch my drift.
A carnal demon truly falling
in love with a saint...
Romantic, don't you think?
Oh...
That's all you have to say?!
Either way, he's after you.
For another chance at the love
he was denied four hundred years ago.
Love...
How about some tea, Miss Saint?
It's important to take breaks, too.
Prince Osvalt...
I'm sorry. I tried to give you a heads-up.
No, that's on me.
My apologies, Your Highness.
Hey, no problem here!
Well... I guess that's not true.
My brother told me about the knights.
That, plus the situation in Girtonia
and Archdemon Asmodeus...
We've got nothing but problems.
Still, if I could ask you for just one
thing... Don't bear this alone.
Miss Philia, you've got me—
I-I mean, everyone in Parnacorta to help!
We're all here for you.
Yes! Yes!
Right.
I'm not sure why,
but Prince Osvalt's words calm me
as much as the aroma of this tea.
Saint Philia.
Once this is all over...
Could we go out together again?
For a meal, this time.
An invitation to dinner?!
Could this be... Don't tell me!
I would be most pleased
to accompany you for a meal.
Saint Philia!
Really? That's great!
One more thing to look forward to!
Why is it that when I see him smile...
Something wrong?
N-No.
He's really holding a party
at a time like this!
Against unprecedented crisis,
this was meant to rally us,
banding us together in our struggle.
But there's no sign of that here.
They're all acting like nothing's wrong,
even with the Demon Realm's
approach peaking at any moment.
Still, that's all the more reason
to give them a wake-up call.
I'll show them the truth
and muster all the kingdom's resources
for the incoming demon horde!
The question is, will it be in time?
Would you like to escape?
I won't run away.
Because this is my revenge.
Hey there, Mia!
You look even more beautiful than usual!
You'll stick with me tonight, won't you?
Yes, of course!
We're engaged, after all!
You seem to be in high spirits.
Are you enjoying this "party"
of yours that much, Julius?
If it isn't my dear elder brother!
I'm so glad to see you feeling so well.
Parties are a wonderful thing.
Especially this one...
A party with the mission
of bringing us all together!
It's Prince Fernand.
So the rumors of his return are true?
You think his health will hold out?
I am Crown Prince Fernand!
I'm sorry to have worried you all for so long.
With my father taken ill,
I'm sure we all feel the threat
to our kingdom ever more keenly.
But worry not!
I swear to do everything in my power
to help us ride out this crisis!
Join me, all of you!
I'm glad I made it through.
You were amazing...
Your Highness!
That was a brilliant speech, dear brother!
Was it?
Pardon me.
I'm going to take my medicine.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll be back for the toast.
I know, Mia.
Let's pick a date for our wedding reception
and announce it to everyone here!
My, what a wonderful idea!
Still, there's no telling how
long this emergency will last...
It might be wise to wait until
the worst has passed, at least.
You worry too much!
But fret not! We'll have good news very soon.
Everything that's about to happen
is for our future together!
Now, let the party begin!
Come, Brother. Let's have a toast.
Surely one glass won't set
your recovery back, will it?
Now, as we all pledge our
loyalty to the royal family
and the eternal prosperity
of the Kingdom of Girtonia...
A toast!
Cheers!
Julius, what did you...?
Farewell, Brother.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Prince Fernand!
Call a doctor! Hurry!
Highness!
He's... not breathing.
No pulse, either.
No... Your Highness!
No, we can... We can still save him!
I'll put my heart and soul
into a resurrection spell!
If I act before his soul leaves
his body, I can save him!
Mia, wait for the doctor.
Don't do anything foolish.
There's nothing we can do.
But if I can do this—
Really, there's need for that.
Why won't you let me do it?
Because I don't want you to.
Do you realize what you're saying?!
He's effectively admitting that he did it!
Prince Julius... we should
hear from the king about this.
Yes, we should.
Assuming he's still alive.
You know the state he's been in.
And besides...
The castle guard is light tonight
with so many of their number diverted here.
If someone were to try something,
we should be receiving word just about now.
What are you saying?
I have a report!
His Majesty... is dead!
I did it! I did it!
Now I'm the king! No one can refuse me!
They were in the way!
My father who denied me the throne!
My brother who refused
to abdicate despite his illness!
I was so sick of both of them!
Let this be an example as well.
This is what happens
when you stand in my way!
Oh, I feel so liberated!
Why...
Why would you go to such
lengths for the throne?
Why? That's obvious.
As everyone knows,
the world exists to serve me.
And Mia!
As my beloved, I gift you the queenship!
Aren't you overjoyed?
My Mia, let's get married this instant!
Mia!
Come on!
I'm afraid I can't let that happen!
Y-You...
How are you still alive?!
It wasn't a resurrection spell,
I can assure you.
You see...
I knew you were planning this all along!
The night of the party, he's going
to try to kill both Fernand and the king?
Why are you telling me this?
To protect our kingdom!
I wasn't the only one afraid for the kingdom.
Knowing this was coming,
I was able to prepare.
I took the antidote when
I stepped away briefly.
This is stage blood.
I pretended to drink the wine,
then burst the packet I had ready
and fell over dramatically.
A compelling performance, no?
As you can see, I am completely unharmed.
B-Brother, you do love to joke around...
Our father's alive as well.
Wh-What?!
Those assassins you sent...
should be getting a taste
of their own medicine now.
What in the world?
There's no justifying this...
It's high treason!
Even as a prince,
it will be his head for this.
Sounds like you've earned a death sentence.
And you tied the noose for yourself
when you tried to kill us.
Sh-Shut up!
An incompetent shut-in like you...
I'm superior to you in every way!
The kingdom's better off
with me on the throne!
What's wrong with getting rid
of who would stop me?!
What's wrong with killing you?!
Everyone would rather have me
on the throne than you!
Oh?
Look at them now and say that again.
Are you idiots going to turn on me, too?!
Now it begins.
Indiscriminate punishment for all
those who betrayed my sister.
Mia!
You joined him because he pressed you, right?
Please, you're my wife!
You have to help me!
If the saint vouches for me...
You have it backward.
Take him to the heights of ecstasy,
give him a long leash,
and then, when I deem the time to be right...
Mia?
It wasn't Prince Fernand
who came up with this plan.
It was me!
I'll betray him.
To take down a member of the royal family,
there needs to be a crime
and unambiguous proof.
I needed to stage a performance
with all here as witnesses.
In addition, I needed everyone—supporters
of both princes, as well as the neutrals—
to come together across political lines
and understand the danger we're facing.
Plotting to kill His Majesty
and the crown prince...
Prince Julius, you are guilty!
This is an indisputable fact.
M-Mia? What are you saying?
You're my wife—
Second Prince Julius Girtonia.
As you are a criminal,
under the laws of our kingdom...
our engagement is officially terminated!
T-Terminated?!
Y-You're turning on me, your dearest love?!
Your gullibility knows
no bounds, Your Highness.
Me, love the man who
sold away my precious sister?
Kindly refrain from saying
such revolting things.
N-No!
I love you!
Marry me and I'll make you so happy!
You know nothing about
what would make me happy!
Mia!
Wh-What are you doing?
Doing this to us... to His Highness!
Why do something so idiotic?!
Why?
Why, you ask?
You treated Philia like garbage!
And you have the nerve to ask me that?!
You asked so much of her
and treated her so coldly.
Then, in the end, you threw her out
and sold her to another kingdom!
She worked so hard to earn the love of the
people she believed to be her parents...
Yet you so happily trampled all over that.
I cannot brook that,
even if you are my parents!
My sister was the perfect saint.
She did so much for our kingdom.
But she was also an ordinary girl,
no different than the rest of us!
Why can't you understand?!
Give her back.
Give her back...
Give back my sister!
Mia...
Did she say Philia?
Why must you bring her up now, of all times?
Ever since I was a child,
I believed myself to be superior.
Academics, fencing... I mastered everything
without the slightest effort.
Amazing, Your Highness!
You have a gift!
It's a sign of superior blood!
I soon learned I wasn't like other people.
I was something special.
The only one who refused to see that...
Julius, work on your attitude.
...was my father.
But what did that matter?
My brother, Fernand, was sickly,
incompetent, worthless.
I was the one with the superior
blood, the gift, the genius!
The perfect prince to whom all should bow!
That's what I believed.
Yes... until that day.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Philia Adenauer.
I knew it at first sight.
That woman was my enemy.
A monster come to shatter
my absolute perfection.
That's why I sold her off.
I could again be the perfect prince...
No, the perfect king!
And yet...
Why must I be hindered, even now?!
I can't accept this.
I won't let that woman beat me!
I am the one with superior blood!
I'm royalty!
You really had me fooled, Mia!
However...
You'll be the one thrown into prison!
For trying to set me up!
Prince Julius, don't humiliate
yourself any further.
Everyone present is a witness
to your foolishness.
You're the foolish one here!
Deceiving the king is a crime,
don't you know that?!
Someone!
Anyone! Take these two into custody!
We just need to silence her testimony!
If you help me, I'll reward you
with anything you want!
Someone!
Some—
Haven't you shamed yourself enough, Julius?
You, old man! You'd better
not talk to me like that!
Do you know who I—
Do you know who I am?!
Don't tell me you've forgotten
your own father's face!
H-His Majesty?!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 10:
Next Time
Episode 10
"What I Wish to Protect"
"What I Wish to Protect."